A Finding Aid to the Garry Knox Bennett Papers, 1917-2017, bulk 1960-2017, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Exhibition Files, 1979-2017; Series 3; Archival Resource Key; 1.4 Linear feet Boxes 3-4
  - Turned Multiples III (2003), Wood Turning Center, Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - 50/50: The Craft Continuum (2004), Lynn Tendler Bignell Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - The Poetry of Light: A Survey of Contemporary Lighting (2004), Savannah College of Art and Design, Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Dovetailing Art and Life: The Bennett Collection (2005), San Francisco Museum of Craft and Design, 2003-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 52-55)
  - Scents of Purpose: Artists Interpret the Spice Box (2005), Contemporary Jewish Museum, 2004-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Turning Around the World (2005-2006), Wood Turning Center, Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Inspired by China (2006-2007), Peabody Essex Museum, 2005-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 58-59)
  - Garry Knox Bennett: Call Me Chairmaker (2006-2009), Traveling Exhibition, Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 1-3)
  - Craft in America: Expanding Traditions (2007), Traveling Exhibition, 2003-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 4-5)
  - M. Lee Fatherree's Photography: Evidence of Artists at Work, 1978-2007 (2007-2008), San Francisco Museum of Craft and Design, 2004-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - One of Each (2008), Gallery NAGA, 2008-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - The Far Side of Function: Contemporary Works in Wood (2009), Dairy Barn Arts Center (Athens, Ohio), 2009-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - New Works / Old Story: 80 Artists at the Passover Table (2009), Contemporary Jewish Museum, 2008-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Twirlings (2009), American Association of Woodturners, 2007-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 10-11)
  - Architectural Digest Home Design Show (2010), Pier 94, 2009-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Baulines Craft Guild Master Show (2010), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Craft in America Silver Dollar City 50th Anniversary Exhibition (2010), Traveling Exhibition, Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Form and Function (2010), The Atrium @ 600 Townsend, 2009-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Gifted Hands: The Fine Art of Craft (2010), Hearst Art Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Golden State of Craft: California 1960-1985 (2011-2012), Craft and Folk Art Museum, Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Postmodernism (2011-2012), Victoria and Albert Museum, 2010-2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 18-19)
  - Beyond Containment (2012), Gallery of Wood Art, 2011-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Do Not Destroy: Trees, Art, and Jewish Thought (2012), Contemporary Jewish Museum, 2009-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Wood (2012), Velvet da Vinci, 2012-2015; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Robin Wood's Cores Recycled: Exhibition and Fundraiser (2012-2013), Center for Art in Wood, 2012-2017; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Garry Knox Bennett: Selected Works-a Broad Spectrum-1963-2013 (2013), Sanchez Art Center, Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Contemporary Crafts Market (2014), Pasadena Convention Center, Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Garry Knox Bennett Illumination (2014), B. Sakata Garo, Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - 50 Years of Works (2015), Snyderman-Works Gallery, 2014-2015; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - California Handmade: State of the Arts (2015), Maloof Foundation, 2015-2017; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - California Wood Artist: Maloof and Beyond (2016), Maloof Foundation, Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - "Chair Prospectus" (2016), Center for Art in Wood, 2011-2016; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - The Spotlight: Functional Lighting as Illuminated Sculpture (2016), Craft in America Center, Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Multiple Exhibitions, California Design, 1976-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Multiple Exhibitions, Mint Condition Gala and Auction, Mint Museum of Craft and Design, 1999-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Multiple Exhibitions at Mobilia Gallery, 1990-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Multiple Exhibitions, SOFA (Sculpture Objects Functional Art and Design), 2008-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Professional Files, 1959-2017; Series 4; Archival Resource Key; 5 Linear feet Boxes 4-9; 0.272 Gigabytes ER0003-ER0004
  Files titled with the names of museums, galleries, and organizations consist of correspondence, loan forms, artwork lists, contracts, printed materials, and other material related to various activities in which Bennett was involved. Other files are for donations, grant proposals, juror and panelist roles, projects and publications, and studio visits and tours. Also included are artist statements by Tom Farber written under the pseudonym Tomaso Fabrizzi for Bennett's jeweler and painter pseudonyms Gerraldo Bennucci and Ambrose Pillphister. Bennett disliked writing artist statements and often looked to other people to write them for him. Bennett's close friend and writer Jack Marlowe wrote several tongue-in-cheek statements for Bennett that became widely distributed and included in articles about Bennett that took snippets from these statements. The Bennetts thought that statements did not read well when partially printed in an article, therefore they stopped sending Marlowe's statements to journalists. The series also includes digital formats including digital video recordings of an interview with Bennett for the Oakland Museum.
  - Alameda Art Center, circa 2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - American Craft Council, 1992-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - American Craft Council, 1985-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - American Craft Museum, 1979-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 2-3)
  - American Furniture Design Co., 1994-2015; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 4-5)
    Includes Bennett's Calico/Trestle table project plans.
  - Anchorage Museum of History and Art, 1991-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Anderson Ranch Art Center, 1996-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Arizona Western College, circa 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Artisan Shop, 1977-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Artists' File, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Artist Statements, General, 1998-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Artist Statements, Correspondence with Bill Krause, 1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Artist Statements for Gerraldo Bennucci and Ambrose Pillphister by Tomaso Fabrizzi (Tom Farber), 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Artist Statements by Bennett for Jack Marlowe, 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Artist Statements for Reproduction, 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Art Programs Inc., 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Aspen Art Museum, 1985-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Banaker Gallery, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Baulines Craft Guild, 1986-2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Bellevue Arts Museum, 2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Bolinas Museum, 2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Branson School, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Brendan White Gallery, 1984-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Brookfield Craft Center, 1984-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - California College of Arts and Crafts, 1959-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - California College of Arts and Crafts, Alumni Show, 2006-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - California Contemporary Craft Association (Formerly Baulines Craft Guild), 1984-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - California Crafts Museum, 1988-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Carol Hooberman Gallery, 1984-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Clark Gallery, 1990-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Contemporary Arts Center (Cincinnati), 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Contemporary Craft Gallery (Portland, Oregon), 1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Craft Alliance Gallery (St. Louis), 1983-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Craft and Folk Art Museum (Los Angeles), 1977-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Crocker Art Museum, 1999-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - de Young Museum, 1999-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Donations, 1970-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 37-39)
  - Dootson / Calderhead Gallery, 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Elaine Potter Gallery, 1985-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Elements Gallery, 1981-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Elizabeth Fortner Gallery, 1978-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Esther Saks Gallery, 1984-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Fendrick Gallery, 1986-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Foster Goldstrom Gallery, 1984-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Franklin Parrasch Gallery, 1990-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
  - Fuller Craft Museum, 2004-2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Furniture Society, Advisory Board, 1999-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Furniture Society, Award of Distinction Records, 2003-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Furniture Society, Conferences, 1997-2016; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 6-11)
  - Furniture Society, Fundraising Auction, 2003-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Furniture Society, General, 1998-2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 13-14)
    Includes transcript of interview with Garry and Sylvia Bennett.
  - Gallery Fair, 1981-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Gallery Concord, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Gallery NAGA, 1989-2012; Archival Resource Key; Includes born-digital records from folder 18, see ER0003. (Box 6, Folder 17-19)
  - NAGA Selections, Digital Photographs, 2008; Archival Resource Key; 0.25 Gigabytes 16 computer files (Box ER0003)
  - Getty Center, Conferences, 2006-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - "GBK" Stationary Orders, 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Grant Proposals, circa 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Gumps Gallery, 1974-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Haystack Mountain School of Crafts, 1991-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Herron Gallery Indianapolis Center for Contemporary Art, 1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Jeffrey Spahn Gallery, circa 2008; Archival Resource Key; Includes born-digital material, see ER0004. (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Gallery Inventory, Digital Photographs and Document, 2007-2008; Archival Resource Key; 0.022 Gigabytes 252 computer files (Box ER0004)
  - Jewish Museum San Francisco, 1997-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Joanne Lyon Gallery, 1987-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Joanne Rapp Gallery / The Hand and the Spirit, 1983-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - John Michael Kohler Arts Center, 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - John Natsoulas Gallery, 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Julie: Artisans' Gallery, 1973-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Juror, Association of Woodworking and Furnishings Suppliers, 2010-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Juror, California State Fair, 2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Juror, Marin County Fair, 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Juror, Western Design Conference, 2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Kaiser Center Art Gallery, 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Kendall College of Art and Design, 2001-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Kentucky Art and Craft Foundation, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Leo Kaplan Gallery, 1996-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 6-8)
  - LIMN, 2008-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Mailing Lists, 2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Marc Adams School of Woodworking, 2004-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Margolis Gallery, Congregation Beth Israel, 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Monterey Peninsula Museum of Art, 1987-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Montreal Museum of Fine Arts, 2009-2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Museum of Fine Art Boston, 1986-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, 1984-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Neuberger Museum, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Norman Petersen Associates, 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - North Light Gallery, 1986-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Oakland Museum, Craft Curator, 1994-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Oakland Museum, "An Afternoon with Garry Knox Bennett 6/9/01" Interview, 2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 21)
    Includes 2 video cassettes (VHS). Duplicates.
  - Oakland Museum, General, 1977-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 22-23)
  - Pacific Rim Sculptors Group, 1992-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Panel, American Association of Woodturners Symposium, 2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Panel, "Critical Discourse on Studio Furniture: Concept and Content" at SOFA Chicago, 2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Parachute Market, 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Patina Gallery, 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Penland School of Crafts, 1992-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Petaluma Arts Council, 2010-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Peter Joseph Gallery, 1992-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 31-35)
  - Pittsburgh Center of the Arts, 1983-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Pritam and Eames, 1988-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Project, Film by Brandon Murray, 2015; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Project, Harrah's Tahoe Hotel, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Project, Hospice Mask Project, 2001-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Project, White Ash Tree Project for Children's Tree and Art Foundation, 2009-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Publication, 500 Cabinets Book by Lark Crafts, 2007-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Publication, Art for Everyday by Patricia Conway, 1982-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Publication, Article and Interview with Bennett by Michael Stone, 1981-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Publication, Article in American Woodturner by Bennett, 2015; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Publication, Departures Magazine, 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Publication, Fine Woodworking Magazine, Traunton Press, 1980-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Publication, "Function and Façade: Furniture and Furnishings by Contemporary Artists" by Michael Hosaluk, 2001-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Publication, Furniture with Soul by David Savage, 2008-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Publication, Louis O'Roberts Book, 2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Publication, General, 1975-2016; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 13-14)
  - Racine Art Museum, 2006-2016; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Renwick Gallery, 1990-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 16-17)
  - Renwick Gallery / James Renwick Alliance, 1997-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 18-19)
    Includes material for the Masters of the Medium Awards.
  - Rhode Island School of Design, 1982-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Richmond Art Center, 2005-2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Rochester Institute of Technology, 2006-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - San Francisco Craft and Folk Art Museum, 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - San Francisco Museum of Art / Aaron Betsky, 1992-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - San Francisco Museum of Craft and Design, Annual Auction, 2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - San Francisco Museum of Craft and Design, Museum Store, 2009-2016; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - San Jose Institute of Contemporary Art Auction, 2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Saskatchewan Craft Council, 1992-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Seb Hamamjian Inc., 2009-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Signature Gallery, 1980-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Slide Requests and Lists, 1984-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Snyderman-Works Gallery, 1981-2017; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 32-34)
  - Society of Arts and Crafts / Society for Art in Crafts`, 1984-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Space Pop Gallery, Grand Opening, 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Spark Art Series, KQED, 2004-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Studio Visits and Tours, 1981-2016; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 1-4)
  - Studio Visit, Museum of Arts and Design San Francisco and Napa / Sonoma Tour, 2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Sun Gallery, 1993-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - T. Delaney Landscape Company, 1987-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Tempe Art Center, 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Tercera Gallery (Palo Alto), 2000-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Tercera Gallery (San Francisco), 1999-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Toledo Museum of Art, 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Transamerica Corporation, 1981-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Travel, 1980-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 13-16)
  - Triton Museum of Art, 1984-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - University of Berkeley Museum of Art at Blackhawk Plaza, 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Various Professional Activities, 1973-2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 19-21)
  - Various Workshop and Lecture Records, 1981-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Virginia Breier, 1977-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Visiting Artist, Indiana University of Pennsylvania, 2010-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Weinberg Gallery, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Wharton Esherick Museum, 1989-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Winfield Gallery, 2003-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Wood Turning Center, 2001-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Worcester Center for Crafts, 1980-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Workbench Gallery, 1980-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Works Gallery, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Yuma Symposium No. 8, 1986-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Zara Gallery, 1976-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Made in Oakland: The Furniture of Garry Knox Bennett Retrospective, circa 1977-2009; Series 5; Archival Resource Key; 1.5 Linear feet Boxes 9-11
  The 2001 retrospective of Bennett's work was first exhibited at the American Craft Museum in New York before traveling to the Oakland Museum. Files include correspondence, fundraising records, publicity, loan agreements, and material regarding photographs and slides. Lender files contain correspondence with collectors requesting to visit their homes in order to assess the works they own by Bennett for possible use in the exhibition, photographs of artwork, printed material, forms, and notes.
  A large portion of the series contains material regarding the creation of a book that also served as the catalog for the retrospective. Initially, the American Craft Museum was tasked with developing the book, but after some debate over pricing the remainder of the book's development fell into the hands of the Bennetts. They worked with curator Ursula Neuman, designer Mark Ong, and editor Fronia Simpson to finish the book. The book includes an exhibition history compiled by Elizabeth Bard and a chronology by John Marlowe.
  - American Craft Museum, 1997-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Attorney for the Arts, Brad Bunnin, 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Book, General, 1998-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 2-3)
  - Book, Bibliography and Exhibition History Compiled by Elizabeth Bard, 1985-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Book, Caption Notes, 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Book, Costs, 2000-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Book, Ed Marquand, 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Book, Essay Drafts by Arthur Danto and Edward S. Cooke, Jr., 1996-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Book, Essay Material, 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Book, Fronia Simpson, 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Book, Idea Books Amsterdam, 2001-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Book, Nancy Fuller, 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Book, Nancy Preu, 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Book, Order and Sales Binder, 2001-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 14-15)
  - Book, Proposal, 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Book, Sales, 2008-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Book, Tom Toldrian, 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Checklists, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Chronology Material, circa 1977-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, General, 1991-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence Regarding Artwork Visits, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, Phil Hanes, 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, Thank You Letters, 2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Curator, Ursula Neuman, 1995-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - European Venues, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Expenses, 2000-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Funding Contributions, 1996-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Fundraising, Corporate, 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Fundraising, Private Donors, 1996-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Lender Inquiries, 1996-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Lender, Agnes Bourne, 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Lenders, E-F, 1994-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Lenders, Martin Foster, 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 1)